Stephen Caldwell

Stephen Caldwell

18 Clonrath Green, Lusk, Co. Dublin, K45 NW21

+353 (87) 392 7768 stephencaldwell137@gmail.com

Profile

Due to Covid 19 I unfortunately was made redundant from my position as an accounts assistant. I found another job rather quickly as a general operative. I currently work as a goods in operative. I decided to look at my redundancy as an opportunity to learn new skills. I have worked in customer service, sales, accounts, credit control, and warehousing. I have experience in many areas and I am not afraid of hard work.

Experience

EZ Living Furniture / Goods In Operative

June 2020 - PRESENT, Damastown, Dublin 15

- Loading and unloading delivery vehicles, by hand or with a forklift truck
- Check goods in against delivery notes for accuracy and damages
- Move goods to relevant departments using pallets trucks and forklifts
- Ensure all stock movements are accurately recorded
- Review customer returns
- Maintain yard and department tidiness/recycle the cardboard

Keogh's Crisps / General operative

April 2020 - June 2020, Oldtown, Co. Dublin

- Working on the crisps production line
- Pack stock into boxes and label boxes
- Sort boxes for shipping

Ace Express Freight / Accounts Assistant

April 2019 - April 2020, Lusk, Co. Dublin

- Reconcile accounts
- Credit control, proactively contacting aged debtors to clear account balances
- Set up new customer accounts
- Take payment for prepay bookings
- Invoice Customers

Ace Express Freight / Junior Sales Assistant

December 2018 - April 2019, Lusk, Co. Dublin

Actively chase and follow up on leads

- Take payment for prepay bookings
- Assist credit account customers with booking forms
- Quote customers via email, telephone and in person

Cartrawler / Customer Service Representative

October 2017 - December 2018, Windy Arbour, Dublin 14

• Support customers needs through a variety of channels such as phone, email, and online

chat

- Achieve individual & team weekly and monthly sales targets
- Ensure customers are fully aware of the agreed payment terms
- Make and manage bookings for customers
- Build rapport with customers to build loyalty for future bookings
- Make appropriate notes after each customer interaction
- Assist with post pick-up queries
- Assist and help new team members when they are assigned to shadow me
- Maintain a high level of confidentiality and ensure GDPR and compliance requirements

are met

Education

Code Institute / Diploma in Full Stack Software Development

November 2020 - Present, Dublin

Awards

High Level Order Picker Licence

References

Aidan Kenny (CFO), Ace Express Freight

akenny@ace-express.com

01 870 2600

Emma Paunia (Sales Team Manager), Cartrawler

epaunia@cartawler.com

01 499 9611

Tom O'Callaghan (Dublin Manager), Eventsec

dublinmanager@eventsec.co.uk

+44 28 9076 6084